Okay, what up, y'all? We're back with a
brand a new video. Make sure you like
and subscribe if you appreciate the
content. I'll be spamming a couple of
new workflows on this new channel. Just
to, you know, get the pace back up.
We've been
bleeding, you know, subscribers on the
paid platform. So, we're going to push
hard.
Yeah, today we have this
clothes clothes changing workflow, we
could say. So, you put in your image of
your clothing, you put an image of your
character,
and the workflow will essentially place
the clothing on your character. Pretty
simple in theory and the workflow as
well. It's nothing too crazy. It's only
this.
And I have a couple of examples of
clothing we're going to be testing in
this video. It's not going to be a long
one. I'm just going to go over
all of the six examples and that's going
to be it.
If you want to grab the free workflow,
just sub on school on the free school in
the link in the description. If you want
to sub workflow, you can just sub
on the school. It's $12.
And you'll get access to all my sub
workflows, this one included. And you'll
be able to essentially put more than one
reference for the clothing. So, if you
want, let's say jacket, glasses, and a
hat, for example, you could do that all
in one go. You can do this yourself.
It's not really hard. You just need to
add, you know, reference latents and VAE
encoders. I'll plug them in together and
they should be good. So,
I'll run the testing with
I guess the second one. We already have
this one here.
As we can see here, we have a little bit
of a consistency issue. The hair goes
through the hoodie. But,
if you run it a couple of times, you'll
you'll eventually get it proper.
So, yeah, let's do the LV jacket here.
Then we're going to do the Astro Astro
Boy.
Then this this this.
And this is the one that's the more
interesting to me. I didn't even try it
yet. But there's a lot of details and I
want to see how it does, you know,
preserving those details. So let's get
it.
Okay, so for the LV jacket, um
first of all, we want to make sure that
we have high resolution images. In this
case, it's not really the highest
resolution except this one.
I grab I grab those from Patreon. Not
Patreon, Pinterest. So you can just go
on Pinterest and just search for
whatever type of clothing you want.
You'll find something. You just copy
paste it back in comfy UI and then you
can just use it as a reference. In this
case, for the prompt,
this is the base prompt. Place the piece
of clothing on the model and we're going
to say also remove the tag.
Because there is a tag on the actual,
you know, jacket. So we're just going to
run this
and
we'll see what we get. Okay, so there's
a little bit of consistency issues with
the original clothing piece of clothing.
As you can see here. But
I think it's pretty good still.
We are using a consistency lower, but if
we turn that off, I think it might help
with the actual consistency of the piece
of clothing. As opposed to the
consistency of the face
because the face didn't really change at
all.
So let's try that here.
The same seed. The only difference is
going to be
um
the consistency lower turned off. We are
using the rest to as
sampler. So that's why it's a little bit
slower. But this result is definitely
better
Uh to the prior one, which disappeared.
Unfortunately, we can't really compare,
but
uh I think this is better. So, I'll
remove that for uh the pri- the the
workflow release. Don't need that if
it's not being useful. Let's try the
next one here, the Astro Boy
uh hoodie.
So, just connect it to the VAE encode
here, and that's all you really have to
do.
The piece of clothing is not, you know,
set in a traditional way like the other
one. So, we'll see how it does with this
type of
uh reference. The scaling might be, you
know, bad or not the best. That's one
thing I see.
Uh and it's not a hoodie. This is just
basically a long long-sleeve t-shirt. Um
so, it's not the best with this uh
example. Uh let's try the the other one.
Uh I'm sure I could say it's a hoodie,
blah blah blah, and it would get it
right. But, this is just with a simple
prompt. Just making it as easy uh on the
prompting side as possible.
Uh so, yeah. Uh this is kind of a jacket
with uh you know, details and stuff. So,
we're trying to see if the details are
going to be represented properly.
Uh
and the design also. This is going to be
important for this one and this one.
This one has a lot of detail. So, we're
going to see how it does with preserving
the details. Um
you know, in the final image.
Uh so, yeah.
Maybe this image is not the best for
this example specifically, but the rest
seems not that bad, honestly.
Um
I think this probably one one of your
better options right now if you don't
have a pipeline for this.
Uh this could be your better option
uh until something better comes out.
Yeah.
Okay. So, now let's try the pink design
hoodie here.
It's a pretty low-res image, so let's
see what we get out of it.
Let me just change the randomize the
seed here.
I think this as well is not being
considered as a hoodie, which it is.
So,
we could specify that here in the
prompt. I'll do it for the the sake of
the example. And we can say that she has
the hood on her head. Technically, it
should work as well. So, let's try that.
She has the hood on her head.
Oh, that's not what I wanted. Okay,
let's try that.
Oh, as you can see, we get the hood on
the head.
It looks pretty good. At first glance
like this, I think it looks not that
bad.
Might make the head look a little bit
big, but aside from that, it's it's
okay, I think. Let's see the full res.
Yeah, I think that's not bad, honestly.
You're not getting this out of anything
else, so
that's pretty much where it ends
if you can't get anything better out of
any other solution. And the design is
actually pretty on point.
Everything is pretty much the same
except the little text here.
But that's really hard to do for, you
know, a low-res reference like that.
And let's try with the last one here.
For this one, I really want to see a lot
of detail, a lot on the text and stuff
like that. It's a pretty high-res
image from the get-go. But it looks like
it might even be AI by itself, honestly.
Maybe, I don't know. I'm not sure. Um
but let's try it. Uh
this is not a hoodie this time, so I'm
going to remove that from the prompt.
Let's just run that.
Okay, so we got the result here. Let's
compare it to the actual jacket.
Um
So, first thing I see
the icon seem to be at the right spot,
um but there's there are some
consistency issues, especially where the
the logos are kind of, you know, messed
up because of the way the the jacket is
placed. Uh there there is a lack of
consistency there, but for example, the
pedigree
logo is pretty good.
Um the two characters here are
okay, but we can see issues especially
on the yellow one
uh
because it kind of missed some of the
information
due to
the way the thing's placed. So, yeah,
it's not that It's not the best.
I I mean, it's probably the best you'll
ever get uh as of right now, but it's
not, you know, foolproof. You do have to
play around with it, and you might have
to play with
you know, the prompts here and there.
But yeah, if you get a piece of clothing
that is, you know, clearly laid out
without any kind of
loss of information like this or this or
this, uh you should be good to go with
this workflow. So, yeah, that's pretty
much it. I'm going to stop yapping. Uh
like I said, join the [__]
[__] me. Join the school. Join the
Discord. And uh I'll see you in the next
one, man. Peace. Appreciate y'all.